<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Achinth</title><link>/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Achinth</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>achinth@student.ubc.ca (Achinth Bharadwaj)</managingEditor><webMaster>achinth@student.ubc.ca (Achinth Bharadwaj)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:33:58 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It’s not just about the code: a lesson in product vision from DubHacks 2020.</title><link>/dubhacks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:33:58 -0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>/dubhacks/</guid><description>The funny thing is, when I was choosing my major, my father told me studying vanilla computer science would be insufficient in the long run for my career. It’s not just about the ability to solve a problem, or randomly blowing out techniques and technologies when solving humankind’s problems; he apprised me to have a vision about what problems that I wanted to solve, how to solve them, and most importantly, how and whom it would help.</description></item><item><title>The system is rigged. It was never fair. It’s ten dimensional chess.</title><link>/gorge_floyd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 18:55:27 -0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>/gorge_floyd/</guid><description>My mother, father, ex, uncles and aunts always said I’m someone who overanalyzes everything. My mom said that God gave me brains to think too much for my own good. She’s right. I make sure I pay attention to every move, every action, every choice and every decision someone makes or something does. Maybe that’s a fault in my personal and emotional lives (I’m working on it actively) but that’s a story for another day.</description></item><item><title>I’ve decided my goals.</title><link>/goals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:25:00 -0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>/goals/</guid><description>As an annoying five-year-old, I wanted to be an astronaut. After I found out that you would need to withstand the force of 10 times of my (at the time) featherweight, I decided being an astronaut was out of the window. All my childlike aspirations left the window when I my English teachers during my time in India said that I had a knack for writing and drama. Everyone found it hilarious that I wished to be involved in drama and literature (despite showing a knack in the mathematics and science fields).</description></item><item><title>Do I have a story to tell?</title><link>/story_tell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 18:55:27 -0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>/story_tell/</guid><description>I don’t know why I decided to start writing on Medium, but I’d like to think that sometime down the lane, I will bring forth something to talk about. I don’t know what it could be; quite frankly it could be things that happens in my life, or things that I am interested in, or things that I wish to improve about myself. A journey of sorts. I’d like to think my life is worth being labelled as a journey.</description></item></channel></rss>